Guide to the Jaime Davidovich Collection MSS.155
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Materials
  - Series 1D: Jaime Davidovich,Exhibition Catalogs, Publicity, and Press; Oversize
    - "The End: An Idependent Vision of Contemporary Culture 1982-200" at Exit Art. Poster, 2000 (Folder 8)
  - Series 1F: Publication of Jaime Davidovich's Work; Oversize
    - Mediapolis. No2 and no 3. Number 2 includeess "Haciendo dulce de Leche en el Ciberespaccio" by Jaime Davidovich., 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Series 1G: Publications Designed or Printed by Jaime Davidovich; Oversize
    - Random House. Book design drafts, ink on paper, pencil on paper, ca 1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Publicity flier mock up for "Jaime Davidovich Video, Stuart Sherman Fifth Spectacle", 1975 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Jaime Davidovich at Everson Museum of Art, publicity flier mock up., 1977 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Anthology screening of Jaime Davidovich Video Tapes, publicity mock up., undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - "Jaime Davidovich Video Tapes" mock up., undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Series 1H: Jaime Davidovich's Teaching and Presentations; Oversize
    - Chicago Editing Center, Presentation by Jaime Davidovich entitled "Wake Up" addresses "How to become a buisiness person and show esoteric art on Cable Television". Publicity posters and mailing., 1974 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Video/Culture Symposium press originals. Research copies available in folder 452. (Folder 5 Right)
    - University of Iowa, course guide., 1986 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Series 1J: Press, Interviews, and Essays about Jaime Davidovich; Oversize
    - Art Forum, "Jaime Davidovich" by Carolyn Kinder Carr., 1974 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Series 2A: Artists TV Network Publicity; Oversize
    - Kitchen video viewing room, cable review lounge poster., undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Kitchen, SoHo TV video review screening in celebration of successful first season. Poster., undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - SoHo TV brochure, mock ups., undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - SoHo TV posters, two sets of three posters featuring A) Sohn Sanborn, Kit Fitzgerald, John Cage, Richard Kostelanetz, Julia Heyward, Robert Kushner. B) Gregory Battcock, Shigeko Kubota, Richard Foreman, Vincent Trasov. C) Terry Fox, Juan Downey, Rita Myers, Joan Jonas., undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Series 2B: Documentation of Organizational Activity; Oversize
    - USA TV exhibit and conference in Barcelona sponsored by the Institute of American Studies. Poster., 1983 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Series 2C: ATN, TV Magazine, Oversize
    - TV Magazine, Pilot issue covers, mock up., undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Inside front cover, mock up., undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Series 2F: ATN Financial materials; Oversize
    - ATN financial worksheet., 1984 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - ATN financial worksheet., 1985 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Check Register and notes, removed from account book in folder 574., 1985 (Box Drawer 1.A, Folder 572)
  - Series 3A: The Live! Show Production and Presentation Materials; Oversize
    - Art TV, by Dr. Videovich. Work on paper., 1980 (Folder 2 Left)
    - Live! Show collage, "Call now 7576401. You can be the doctor." Multimedia on cardstock., undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - TeeVee cartoon., undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Series 3D: The Live! Show Press and Publicity Materials; Oversize
    - the Live! Show poster., undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Mensajes y Medios magazine.Copy, "Jaime Davidovich, El Humor como arma de reflecion", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Series 3E: Exhibition and Distribution Catalogs; Oversize
    - The Live! Show retrospective at AMMI, schedule of events., 1990 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Series 7B: Other Artists' Announcements and Works; Oversize
    - Heyward, Julia. "Self Portrait" black and white photograph. OVERSIZE, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Series 8B: Subject Files; Oversize
    - Argentina, New York Times Sunday Style section, 9 November 1997 (Box 35, Folder 2)